TRIPTI WANI

Full Stack Web Developer

Telephone +61 481254765 Email tripti.895@gmail.com Address Sydney, Australial Website

PROFILE

Focused and self-motivated professional, with an experience of 7 years in Information Technology, I love to solve problems with code while applying industry best practices in a collaborative environment. Aspiring full stack web developer with a strong interest in projects that require both conceptual and analytical thinking. Fully- committed to designing and developing innovative web-based materials that users will love. Always eager to learn more tricks from anyone - regardless of the industry they're working in.

Technical Skills

HTML CSS

Javascript Backbone.js

jQuery Ruby Underscore.js

Rails Database:

SQL, Postgres

Github Ajax TDD -

Heroku Rspec,

RESTful APIs Cucumber

UNIX Scripting

BootStrap

References

Joel Turnbull, Instructor,GA Bala R., RXP Services Limited

Details are available on request

EXPERIENCE

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

June 2016 - Aug 2016

General Assembly is a pioneer in education and career transformation, specialising in today's most in-demand skills. The leading source for training, staffing, and career transitions, it fosters a flourishing community of professionals pursuing careers they love.

TALK2ME

User friendly web-based chat application covering photos, gifs and location with a Mobile-first approach.

PALATE

A mobile-first app for creating, bookmarking and sharing recipes from any existing recipe websites via chrome extension.

INVENOTRY MANAGEMENT

This is an e-commerce website to procure, track and deal in Mobile handsets and accessories for wholesalers and retailers across multiple locations with the built-in payment feature.

INFOSYS LIMITED

July 2008 - Sep 2015

Infosys Limited is an Indian multinational corporation that provides business consulting, information technology and outsourcing services.

Technology Lead/ Technology Analyst

July 2012 - Sep 2015

- Interactions with the business analysts for analysis and understanding of the technical requirements to be applied
- Performed Requirement Analysis, Design with Development and testing
- Contribution of functional and technical documents to the Knowledge Center
- Provide technical mentoring to the team members, perform reviews artifacts prior to delivery
- Handling Configuration Management and Control
- Worked on the ETL Framework migration

Senior Software Engineer/ Software Engineer July 2012 - Sep 2015

- Creation of source code for conversion and collection programs
- Planning and tracking 24*7 production support cycle
- Respond to and fix production issues within acceptable timelines
- Conduct analysis, and suggest/implement work-around and perform Root Cause Analysis and fixes to avoid re-occurence.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2016	Web Development Immersive
2011 - 2013	General Assembly, Sydney MBA in Human Resource
	Symbiosis, India
2004 - 2008	M.Sc. (Hons.) Chemistry – Integrated Course
	BITS Pilani, India